<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SofiTV</string>
    <string name="title_MovieTrailers">Trailers</string>
    <string name="title_News">News</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">About</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <!--<string name="tv_shows">Channels</string>-->

    <string name="action_sortPopular">Popular Movies</string>
    <string name="action_sortTopRated">Top Rated Movies</string>
    <string name="data_not_available">Data Not Available</string>
    <string name="no_connection">Failed to load data.  Please check connection and try again.</string>
    <string name="action_sortFavorite">Favorite Movies</string>
    <string name="ADD_FAVORITE">Add to Favorites</string>
    <string name="REMOVE_FAVORITE">Remove from Favorites</string>
    <string name="review_not_available">Reviews not available</string>

    <string name="accept">Accept</string>
    <string name="eula_string">COPYRIGHTS:

\nCopyright 2019 SofiTV by ElyOctal. All Rights Reserved.
\n
\nLICENSE AGREEMENT
\n
\nThis application or App entitled \"SofiTV\" may not, in whole or in any part, be copied, reproduced, transmitted, translated (into any language,
        natural or computer), stored in a retrieval system, reduced to any electronic medium or machine readable format, or by any other form or means
        without prior consent, in writing, from SofiTV and its creator ElyOctal.
\n
\nYou are granted a limited license to use this App. The App may be used or copied only in accordance with the terms of that license, which is described in
        the following paragraphs.
\n
\nTRADEMARKS:
\n
\nSofiTV logo is a trademark of SofiTV.
\nTitles, photos , illustrations and articles may be subject to copyright of those who owns it.
\nVideos or channels link in this App are source from different base urls of different sites .
\nSofiTV does not own any videos, channels and contents.
\nMovie trailers, videos, and photos appeared on this app are owned by The Movie Database (TMDb).
\n
\nLICENSE:
\n
\n\"SofiTV\" shall be taken to mean the software contained in this app and any subsequent versions or upgrades received as a result of having
        downloaded this app. \"USER\" shall be taken as the original receiver of the software.
\n
\nUser has the non-exclusive right to the use of the app only on a single device. User may not electronically transfer the program from one device to
        another over any type of network. User may not distribute copies of the app or the accompanying documentation to others either for a fee or without
        charge. User may not modify or translate the program or documentation. User may not disassemble the program or allow it to be disassembled into
        its constituent source code. User\'s use of the software indicates his/her acceptance of these terms and conditions.
\n
\nIf user does not agree to these conditions, return the distribution media, documentation, and associated materials to the vendor from whom the app was
        purchased, and/or uninstall the software from the device, and erase the software from any and all storage devices upon which it may have been installed.
\n
\nThis license agreement shall be governed by the laws of The United States of America, and shall inure to the benefit of SofiTV or its assigns.
\n
\nDISCLAIMER / LIMITATION OF LIABILITY:
\n
\nUser acknowledges that the software may not be free from defects and may not satisfy all of User\'s needs.  The app and any accompanying written
        materials are licensed \"AS IS\". Users exclusive remedy during the warranty period (if any) shall consist of replacement of distribution media if
        determined to be faulty.
\n
\nIn no event will SofiTV be liable for direct, indirect, incidental or consequential damage or damages resulting from loss of use, or loss of
        anticipated profits resulting from any defect in the app, even if it has been advised of the possibility of such damage.The user is advise to verify such
        information or direction before use.
\n
\nSPECIFIC RESTRICTIONS:
\n
\nIn accordance with the COMPUTER SOFTWARE RENTAL ACT OF 1990, this app may not be rented, lent or leased. The app and accompanying
        documentation may not be provided by a \"Backup Service\" or any other vendor which does not provide an original package as composed of
        SofiTV, including but not limited to all original distribution media, documentation, registration cards, and insertions.

</string>
</resources>
